所以我要跳出来摆脱这一切
So I'm gonna type exit to get out of this.
所以现在我回到正常的环境里
So now I'm back in my normal environment,
and
我要做的第一件事就是我要说 ldd/bin/cat
then the first thing I'm gonna
do is I'm gonna say ldd/bin/cat.
你可以忽略这个
You can ignore this one.
它有这个还有这个
It has this one and this one.
事实上，我很确定我们已经复制了这两个。
And I'm actually pretty sure that
we already copied both of these.
所以如果我进入我的新根
So if I go into my new root ls lib,
它要求 libc.so.6 在这里
it's asking for libc.so.6 which is here.
如果我做了 lib64 ，它就能完成它。
And if I do lib64,
it has for so.2, it does.
所以我们其实不用复制任何东西。
So we actually don't
have to copy anything.
他们已经在那里了
They're already there.
所以我现在唯一要做的就是把 /bin/cat 复制到 bin中。
So the only thing I have to do now is
I have to copy from /bin/cat into bin.
现在，如果我看看 bin 里面，你可以看到我也有猫。
And so now if I look inside of bin,
you can see here I have cat as well.
所以现在如果我换个根仓就像那样
So now if I do change root bin per size,
bash like that,
回到我的监狱里
to go back into my jailed process.
我可以看到，我输入的是 ls ，是有用的，现在如果我输入猫咪，
I can see, I type ls, that works and
now if I type cat secret.txt,
它会告诉你我的秘密汽水配方
it tells you my secret soda recipe.
>> 然后，它具有您需要每个副本的二进制文件，获取该二进制文件。
&gt;&gt; So then, it has the binaries that
you need to each copy over, got it.
然后它将使用您复制的库。
And then it will use
the libraries that you copied.
>> 正好，因为它无法到达被监禁的过程之外
&gt;&gt; Exactly, because it cannot reach
outside of the jailed process
能联系到其他的二进制文件
to be able to reach the other binaries.
完全被锁住了
It's totally locked off.
所以你不放进来的东西根本就没放进去
So anything that you don't put in
here doesn't get put in there at all.
>> 因此，当您运行 LDD 时，会列出不同的需求，
&gt;&gt; So when you run LDD and it kind
of lists the different requirements,
为什么我们不能再忽视第一次
why were we able to ignore
the first one again?
> > 我会告诉你，如果我做我的猫，你就可以在这里看到这个吗 ?
&gt;&gt; I will tell you, so if I do l bin cat,
so you can see this one right here?
> > Mm - m.
&gt;&gt; Mm-hm.
>> 如果您询问我们为什么不能忽略它的实际原因，
&gt;&gt; If you're asking for the actual
reason of why we can't ignore it,
我不知道跟你说实话
I don't actually know,
to be honest with you.
我只知道如果它不给你一个完全合格的路径
I just know that if it doesn't give you
a fully qualified path like it does like
那么你就可以自由地无视它了
this, then you're free to ignore it.
>> Cool。
&gt;&gt; Cool.